Keep runnin' along.
Watch as we pass by.
As we raise our flag.
Up high in the sky.
Alright, here we go now.
Sailing through the endless ocean.
Facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure.
Nobody has ever.
Got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep
believing in our dreams.
And let our heart lead the way.
Then once we got all that.
All there's left is to go.
When we face the dark and stormy weather.
Keep the pace.
We'll link our hearts together.
Then I'm sure we'll make it through.
No matter what.
Keep running along, keep running along.
Still raising our flag as we journey on.
Though our chances are close to none.
We won't back down from anyone.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
Toward our own dreams
while keeping the pace.
With a compass pointing to our goal.
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world.
Start me up.
Keep running along, keep running along.
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top.
There's no way that we'll ever quit.
We'll keep heading for tomorrow.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
I see through your eyes,
what we'll have to face.
All the memories will stay in our hearts.
We'll never let them go.
Brand new world.
Let's start me up!
Hey hello damn too late!
That jerk oh wait a second right it doesn't
matter since i know where they're going.
All i gotta do is head to the gates of
justice and i'll catch them in no time!
Why don't you save me
the trouble of cutting
you down you have the key
or not don't be a fool!
You may have been a
bit of a disappointment
back at the galley law
mansion but i expect to
be Entertained this time
if you pirates could
make it this far then
you're far more capable
than i gave You credit
for got that right make
that mistake again and
you'll be dead maybe so
you're like a Beast
that savage look in your
eyes but i can be pretty
beastly myself you know!
For the record i'm the
strongest swordsman in
all of cp9 this won't
be easy two sword style
Tempest kick!
Sorry i use four swords!
Well that's fine by me!
Your whole body is a weapon, isn't it?
What's the difference?
72 caliber.
Tempest kick!
Like...
Shake.
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
This is fun.
Yeah?
Well, I don't have time
for fun right now. Shame.
Guess you'd better kill me quickly then.
Tempest kick. Slaughter!
He's throwing out everything at once.
What is this?
Rastard, are you taking this seriously?
Of course, I'm quite impressed.
But you said you were
in a hurry, didn't you?
My new power should
speed things up for you.
Wh-what the hell?
This sure isn't what I was expecting.
A little gardening is nice and
all, but this is way overboard.
It's like we're outside.
Okay, whatever.
I'm gonna focus on getting
the key to Robin's handcuffs.
Here we go.
Careful, careful.
No, don't stop.
Move in quietly.
Run away quietly.
Take the key and leave a hero.
No need to fight.
That's right, I'm Sniper King,
but today, I'm Lucky King too!
Itty Betty bit, almost there!
And Rooster, are you kidding me?
I'm right there, and the noisiest bird
in the whole stinking world shows up.
If he crows, I'm finished.
That assassin guy will wake
up and wipe the floor with me.
What's that look?
Are you going to crow?
You're going to crow, aren't you?
No, please, please.
Shh, shh.
Rooster, Mr.
Rooster, Master Rooster, sir.
I'm begging you, don't crow.
Don't say a word.
Just take some time and
take it over, please.
Chirp.
Roosters don't chirp.
Come on!
Oh, hey, pirate.
Curse you, rooster.
Guess it's time to kick your ass, then.
Curse you.
Eat strong.
So it's you, huh?
You're the slingshot guy that
burned down the flag, right?
Too bad sniping won't help you here.
He just woke up from his nap and
he's already hitting that hard?
Sorry, pal.
That punch was kinda sloppy. Not my style.
Bet it hurt, though.
I know I look scary, but I'm no sadist.
I like my fights clean and simple.
He's got Devil Fruit powers!
The dog-dog fruit, model wolf.
I'll just tear out your
windpipe, and that'll be that.
You're gonna die anyway, so no
need for you to suffer, right?
See? Simple.
A wolf?
Hmm hold on you sure you
don't look all that tough
Don't try to intimidate me.
I'm not giving up
Got it.
I came to save Robin.
That's what I'm gonna do
I was trying to use my man beast
form, but I messed up on the man part
THE CEILING!
Your power is so awesome!
I love it!
Whoa! What the?
Did you play some kind of zoo?
Oxox fruit! Model giraffe!
Kaku, you poor bastard!
I told you not to eat
that fruit, didn't I?
And what's so wrong with
being a giraffe, huh?
For your information, I
happen to like it, okay?
That pigeon guy was a leopard, wasn't he?
That makes three people
that transform into animals.
Does that mean the rest of
CP9 has powers like that, too?
A wolfman is one thing,
but now a giraffeman, too?
This is insane.
How am I supposed to
deal with two Zonatimes?
Actually, now that Zorro's
here, it's two-on-two, isn't it?
Or more like two-on-one, with this guy
cowering in the corner and watching.
What's that?
Looks like someone left a safe open.
Wait, are those weird-looking
handcuffs what I think they are?
That's enough! Stop
laughing! Hey, giraffe!
Could you shut up?
I'm in a hurry.
If you zoo animals want to
argue, do it on your own time.
But if you just want to stand
there, your neck is an easy target.
You fool.
Don't underestimate the limitless
destructive power of giraffes.
Behold my man-beast form.
I have been reborn with unspeakable power.
Whoa, that is lame! But I... What? No!
Why did I say something so stupid?
I mean, he does look pretty
ridiculous, but that's not the point.
If I lose my composure,
he'll have the advantage.
Are you going to sit there
and laugh all day, or what?
Sorry.
Damn it.
This is harder than I thought.
Why does he have to be so
square and funny-looking?
Huh?
Wait, where did these handcuffs come from?
Ah!
Oh, no! Whoops! Sorry!
What the hell are you trying to pull?
Well, I was thinking,
those are probably the same Z-PRISM
handcuffs they put on ramen!
Our enemies both have devil
fruit powers, you know?
So I thought if I cuffed them,
they'd be easier to beat!
Then why didn't you put
the handcuffs on them?
Why me?
B-Because I...
The giraffe guy's face is too funny! My...
hand slipped!
I'm not square, I'm cool, right?
That's brilliant!
You're going to pay for this!
You're all going to pay!
I'll show you the power of my
Devil Fruit, then you'll be sorry!
Best kick?
Whoa, boy, he's mad now!
Huh?
Sky Slicer!
This isn't good.
Usa, get down!
I see.
That long neck has improved your reach.
The centrifugal force
coming from a body that
size makes for a very fast
and very deadly attack.
Wait a sec.
It doesn't look like
he cut anything to me.
Try taking a look at the ceiling. Huh?
The ceiling?
All I can see is the sky the
sky but that
must mean you
should be ashamed
a Professional
doesn't let his emotions get
the better of it I don't want
to hear It anymore for the
last time giraffes are awesome
I love giraffes fine Whatever
you say man huh you can show
off all you want it doesn't
matter to me I Came here expecting
a fight your powers don't
scare me one bit okay cut it
out Zoro that hurts what are
you doing why are you pulling
my arm like that wait Hey,
my arm!
Whoa, that's not coming off.
Nope, don't think so.
What the hell did you just do?
I swear this is not my fault!
If you hadn't tackled me back there,
this never would have happened!
You're about to get your hat lopped
off and you're blaming this on me?
Are you trying to get
us both killed or what?
Now they're completely ignoring
us what happened okay okay
let's think about This in short
we're in the same situation
as Robin right right then to
Get the key we're gonna have
to fight them and take it so
nothing has changed Really being
handcuffed to someone is just
business as usual then damn I
guess They're stuck together fine
then it's settled I'll put those
two idiots out Of their misery
you stand over here and watch
what screw you I'm not letting
you steal my prey you bastard.
Our only other option is working
together, and I know you don't want that
That's how I feel.
Hey, you guys Can you check
the number on those handcuffs?
Number?
Each pair of handcuffs and each key is
marked with a matching number Otherwise,
we wouldn't know which key
we need to use to unlock them
At any rate if either of us
have the key to those handcuffs,
we'll unlock them for you.
Oh, okay.
Thanks Let's see, where is it?
Here, it's number two! Unlock us!
No, not mine.
It's not mine either. That's a shame.
Dammit, they don't get
our hopes up like that!
Even if we ran away, it's not like we
could fight the rest of CP9 in this state.
That settles it then.
Guess it's first come, first kill.
That's only fair, I suppose.
Crap!
That's weird. What happened?
The stairs are all split up.
I should have known.
It must have been that
big rumble I felt earlier.
Whoever's fighting sure must be tough.
Hey, are you guys okay in there?
Zoro!
Sniper King!
Hey, Jumper!
Huh?
What's going on?
They're waving at me.
Maybe it's a game.
Yay!
We're stuck together,
stupor, and if you can't find key
number two, they're going to murder us!
Oh, okay.
What the hell is this?
I kind of figured there'd be
a bridge here or something.
Man, those whirlpools are really huge.
I can see the Gates of Justice from here,
but I don't know if I
can get there on a boat?
I don't have time to stand here and
think, I gotta give it a shot at least!
Here goes nothing.
I'm on my way, Robin!
I get it, so the keys and the handcuffs
have matching numbers on them.
If you can't fight, then that's
okay, I didn't find anyone,
so I can just beat these guys for you!
Sorry, but there's no way
in hell that's gonna happen,
and besides, if you get taken out?
We'll be stuck in these
handcuffs with no way to fight.
Please.
We're counting on you.
You're our only hope Only hope?
Flattery doesn't work on me at
all you big dummies Between Sanji,
Nami and Franky someone has
to have the number two key.
Get it and bring it here.
Hurry, okay?
If anyone has a key
already, it's probably Sanji
I've got to find him.
I'm their only hope.
No!
Yo!
I've caught you now, girl!
Let go!
Yo-yo!
You are far too weak!
Now perish!
I'm no match for him at all!
Franky!
Iron body! Foxy!
Why are your punches so strong?
Wait, you're not human, are you?
It's cute how you CP9 guys can
make your bodies hard like iron.
But these fists of mine are
the genuine article, brother!
What am I doing?
This is no time for me to be drinking tea!
Witchcraft!
You put me under a spell!
One more sip and I'd be finished! Damn it!
I almost got captured in your love trap!
So you say, after three cups.
Shut up, you witch!
Don't you dare play innocent with me!
I haven't forgotten what
happened on the C-train.
I won't forgive the way
you people treated Robin.
Now, give me your key.
What a shame.
It seems you're in a hurry.
Well, I won't keep you.
If you want the key, then take it.
So where is it?
Who knows?
You'll have to search my body
and find out for yourself.
Think you're up to it?
You said I am!
You're off to a bad start.
Damn, that was stupid.